Contact

9822857421 (Home) vvmohol@rediffmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vishwajit-mohol-a4227a18 (LinkedIn) thedigitechsolutions.com (Company)

Top Skills

Retail Banking
Credit
Commercial Banking

VISHWAJIT MOHOL

BUSINESSMAN DIGITECH SOLUTIONS
Pune

Summary

Experienced Branch Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the banking industry. Skilled in Banking, Sales, Branch Management, Commercial Banking, and Loans. Strong sales professional with a Master of Business Administration (MBA) focused in Finance, General from Bharati Vidyapeeth. Started my own business in it field .. running my business namely digital marketing services provider and digital marketing training institute, and software and web designing and development

Experience

DIGITECH SOLUTIONSS
BUSINESSMAN
January 2018 - Present (2 years 8 months)
Pune Area, India

WE do provide solutions through Digitech

Digital Marketing services
Digital Marketing training
Software Development
Web Designing and Development

svc bank
branch manager
June 2010 - Present (10 years 3 months)
BRANCH BANKING, CASA, CREDIT, PLANNING SUPERVISION,

PRITHVI PROPERTY AND INVESTMENT CONSULTANT Proprietor

January 2013 - March 2017 (4 years 3 months)

Pune Area, India

WE DEALS IN ALL PROPERTIES IN PUNE , WE ARE IN TO SOLE SELLING REAL ESTATE AGENCY IN PMC AND PCMC AREA

HDFC Bank

branch manager

October 2010 - October 2011 (1 year 1 month)

BRANCH BANKING, CASA, INSURANCE, RECRUITMENT, TARGET ACHIEVEMENT, AUDIT, OPERATION, MARKETING, PLANNING, ADMINISTRATION

PUNE

AXIS BANK

November 2000 - October 2008 (8 years)

RELATIONSHIP MANAGER, BRANCH SALES MANAGER CASA, CASH, MARKETING, INSURANCE SELLING, BRANCH TARGET OVER ALL

Education

Bharati Vidyapeeth

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Finance, General · (1998 - 2000)

Pune University

Bachelor of Commerce (BCom), Business Administration and Management, General · (1996 - 1998)